Hello friends, there are two ways to
launch any business, one
is top down approach and the other is bottom-up approach.
So friends, today we will talk about top-down approach, the
power of interest is that first
you identify the country and identify the travel
industry in it, then see which
stock, which company can do well.
Friends, today we are going to talk about it.
First we will talk about Clothji, after that
we will talk about India. Friends, if you see, today
we are going to talk
about the insurance industry. So friends, if
you see, the global average
of the insurance industry is 2.4 percent of GDP, that is, it is
2.4 percent of the total world GDP. If you compare it with your shoes, then it is six
percent of GDP.
Similarly, if you compare it with China, then it is total
handsfree. So friends, now let's come to
India. If you see, the
processor price of GTA, which is
insurance, is online service percent. That is,
friends, if you see, our
global average salary is much less than  But
friends,
how much is the possibility of its growth? And anyway,
India is a very
fast-growing country, so
friends, that's why I think it can
grow very fast. So friends, if
you have seen since 2004, the
insurance industry is growing at a 60% pace.
60%. Here, friends, when
any industry itself ignores, then you should
see the market leadership in it, if any
company can do such work,
how fast can it grow, friends. So,
for this one company Jyoti is the market leader, it is a
private business man and a private
insurance company. ICICI
Lombard General Insurance, friends, this
company is a 34-year-old industry, it was starting with 60%. The
second company, this company has been
growing since 23 February 2018, it is the market leader. Privacy
Shortcuts Nine has a market share of nine, the
rest of it is PSUs
like United Kingdom and the rest of Oriental Bank,
all these are PSUs, these are market leaders,
but then there are PSU companies.  If you see, the
main profit comes from PSUs, they
never work for bread,
they work to please the customers,
friends and if you
see its vitamins, say 37th of ICICI Lombard,
friends, vitamins, the one
whose W comes, comes, in the same way, in car
insurance, 90% of what comes comes
from symptoms and the rest comes from club,
temperature presenter shows that and dies,
and it also comes from backwards
etc. or in his dreams,
big people also
get protection for them so that if something happens, they
can take benefit from it too, friends, inches
money is available in these and
this marine insurance is supplied without any cover
through the sea, it does post office job,
friends, hence the above mentioned free insurance is
working very well, friends,
if you see that in car insurance,
it has a line of discipline service
centers, that is, if
you only get an answer from the center
where you can get a bicycle car service  It is
coming or you are going to service centers that
after all Jyoti Jhanshyam, if you buy a car
from the showroom, then the insurance you will get there too,
most probably
you will not get such insurance anywhere, that is
because they have got new cases, this
convention is at the showroom and is on board, which has already
started with the exam, so they have
more metro hospitals, so if
you pay their interest then most likely
you will not get your network software
near by Riya, so
friends, Zinc is creating a very good mode
and if you see, the interpress is
ICICI Bank itself, that is, when
these IS back to back, that is only and
only like ICICI Lombard, the general bank
feels that you should keep it, it has a lot of insurance,
so friends, what is your comment about this video,
think about this company, today again
what is your thought about the industry, you
can tell it below by commenting in your video,
friends, like the video, share it,
subscribe to the channel in Hindi